[
  {
    "question": "一",
    "answer": "いち、ひと　One",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "二",
    "answer": "に、ふた　Two",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "三",
    "answer": "さん、み　Three",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "四",
    "answer": "よん、し、よ　Four",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "五",
    "answer": "ご、いつ　Five",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "六",
    "answer": "ろく、む、むい　Six",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "七",
    "answer": "なな、しち、なの　Seven",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "八",
    "answer": "はち、や、よう　Eight",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "九",
    "answer": "九、く、ここの　Nine",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "十",
    "answer": "じゅう、とお　Ten",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "百",
    "answer": "ひゃく　Hundred",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "千",
    "answer": "せん、ち　Thousand",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "万",
    "answer": "まん　Ten-thousand",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "日",
    "answer": "にち、ひ、び, Day, Sun",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "本",
    "answer": "ほん、もと　Book",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 15
  },
  {
    "question": "語",
    "answer": "ご、かたる、がたり　Language, speech, word",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 16
  },
  {
    "question": "何",
    "answer": "なに、なん、か　What",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 17
  },
  {
    "question": "月",
    "answer": "げつ、がつ、つき　Moon, month",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 18
  },
  {
    "question": "火",
    "answer": "か、ひ　Fire",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 19
  },
  {
    "question": "水",
    "answer": "すい、みず　Water",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 20
  },
  {
    "question": "木",
    "answer": "もく、き Tree, wood",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 21
  },
  {
    "question": "金",
    "answer": "きん、かね　Gold",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 22
  },
  {
    "question": "土",
    "answer": "ど　Soil, earth",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 23
  },
  {
    "question": "人",
    "answer": "ひと、にん、じん　Person",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 24
  },
  {
    "question": "時",
    "answer": "とき、じ　Time",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 25
  },
  {
    "question": "分",
    "answer": "ふん、ぶん　Minute",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 26
  },
  {
    "question": "半",
    "answer": "はん　Half",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 27
  },
  {
    "question": "年",
    "answer": "ねん、とし　Year",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 28
  },
  {
    "question": "小",
    "answer": "しょう、ちい　Small",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 29
  },
  {
    "question": "学",
    "answer": "がく、まな　Study, learn",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "校",
    "answer": "こう、きょう Exam, school",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 31
  },
  {
    "question": "生",
    "answer": "せい、いき、うま　Life, birth",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 32
  },
  {
    "question": "中",
    "answer": "ちゅう、なか　Inside, Centre",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 33
  },
  {
    "question": "今",
    "answer": "いま、こん　This, now",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 34
  },
  {
    "question": "才",
    "answer": "さい　Age",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 35
  },
  {
    "question": "行",
    "answer": "こう、ゆ、い　Go, line, act",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 36
  },
  {
    "question": "上",
    "answer": "うえ、あ、じょう　Above, up",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 37
  },
  {
    "question": "下",
    "answer": "した、、くだ、さ　Down, below",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 38
  },
  {
    "question": "左",
    "answer": "ひだり　Left",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 39
  },
  {
    "question": "右",
    "answer": "みぎ　Right",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 40
  },
  {
    "question": "名",
    "answer": "な、めい　Name",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 41
  },
  {
    "question": "前",
    "answer": "まえ、ぜん　Before, in front of, previous",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 42
  },
  {
    "question": "円",
    "answer": "えん、まる、まど　Yen、Circle, Round",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 43
  },
  {
    "question": "男",
    "answer": "おとこ、だん　Male",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 44
  },
  {
    "question": "女",
    "answer": "おんな、じょ　Female",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 45
  },
  {
    "question": "子",
    "answer": "こ　Child",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 46
  },
  {
    "question": "大",
    "answer": "だい、たい、おお　Large, Big",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 47
  },
  {
    "question": "先",
    "answer": "せん、さき、ま　Before, ahead, previous",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 48
  },
  {
    "question": "目",
    "answer": "め　Eye",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 49
  },
  {
    "question": "口",
    "answer": "くち　Mouth",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 50
  },
  {
    "question": "手",
    "answer": "て　Hand",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 51
  },
  {
    "question": "耳",
    "answer": "みみ　Ear",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 52
  },
  {
    "question": "出",
    "answer": "で、だ　Exit, leave",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 53
  },
  {
    "question": "入",
    "answer": "はい、い(る)　Enter, Insert",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 54
  },
  {
    "question": "私",
    "answer": "わたし、し　I, me, private",
    "correct": false,
    "id": 55
  }
]